For this question, you're asked to define two procedures.
对于这个问题 你需要定义两个过程
The first one takes a match as its inputs along with a replacement,
第一个需要输入 匹配 (match) 和替换 (replacement)
and it outputs some sort of structure, which you'll be able to use.
它要输出某种结构 未来可以使用的结构
In the second procedure, apply converter, which will change a string according
第二个程序 apply_converter 它会根据
to the match and replacement.
match 和 replacement 改变字符串
I'll just do an example.
我示范一个例子
aaabaa--if this is our match and replacement, the aba will be replaced with b.
'aaabaa' 如果这是我们的 match 与 replacement 'aba' 将替换为 'b'
The next string we'll have will be aaba.
我们得到的下一个字符串是 'aaba'
Then we've got aba again, so we'll replace that with b.
然后我们再次得到 'aba' 我们将它替换为 'b'
There are no more matches, so we stop.
再也没有更多的匹配 (match) 所以我们停下来
You can see at each step it's changed, and when we change it no more, we stop.
你可以看到每一步所做的改变  当我们无法再改变它 我们就停下来
What our code is going to do is continue.
我们的代码要做的就是继续下去
As long as we've made a replacement at the previous step, we'll do a step again.
只要我们在上一步骤进行更换 我们会做下一步骤
If we haven't made a replacement, then we'll stop.
如果我们没有进行替换 那么就停下来
On to the code.
我们来看代码
What structure do I want?
我需要什么结构呢？
Well, I'm simply going to make a list where the first entry in the list is the match,
嗯 我只要简单地制作一个列表 列表中的第一个项目就是 match
and the second entry is the replacement.
第二个项目是 replacement
Apply_converter has as its input a converter which we made in make_converter.
apply_converter 的输入就是 我们以 make_converter 做出来的 converter
That's a list, and the string that we want to change.
那是一个列表 和我们想要更改的字符串
I said that I was going to continue changing the string as long as the string
我说过 我会继续改变字符串
was not the same as it was before.
只要字符串和以前不一样
We're going to have to keep track of the previous string.
我们要跟踪以前的字符串
At the start there isn't a previous string.
一开始 不存在以前的 (previous) 字符串
While previous is not the same as the current string, I want to carry on with the loop.
当以前的 (previous) 字符串和目前的字符串 (string) 不同  我要继续这个循环
As soon as I enter the loop, I want previous to be equal to string,
一旦我进入循环 我要 previous 等于 string
and then I want to look for the match in the string.
然后我要在字符串里寻找 match 字符串
The position of the math we can find using find,
我们可以使用 find 找到 match 的位置
and we're looking for the first word in the converter.
我们要寻找 converter 的第一个词
If we find it, then we're going to replace our string with a new string,
如果我们找到它 我们要将字符串替换成一个新字符串
which is the first part of the string up to the position, not excluding it--
字符串的第一部分到这个位置 不包括它
the start position of our match.
match 的起始位置
We replace that with the replacement, and finally we want to concatenate
我们以 replacement 做替换 最后 我们要连接
the part of the string after the match.
match 后面的字符串
We find it's position by starting at the beginning of the match
我们从 match 的起始位置开始 找到它的位置
and adding on the length of the match.
加上 match 的长度
Then taking that to the end of the string.
然后 采用字符串直到结尾
As long as we've made a change, the loop continues.
只要我们做了更改 循环继续
If we haven't made a change, the loop ends, and we return the string.
如果我们没有进行更改 循环结束 我们会传回这个字符串